Oh
You know you love me. I know you care
Never
You
Will never ever ever be a part
Oh
Just friends what are you saying?
Said there's another in the right mind
First love
And I was like
Thought you'd always be in my
My baby
Baby
Thought you'd always be my
I would have done whatever and I just can't believe we hang together and I want to play cool
Oh
I'll buy you anything
I'm in peace
Baby fix me and you shake me till you wake me from this bad dream
Going down down down down and I just can't believe my first love will be running
Baby
Thought you'd always be my
Baby baby
Baby
Oh
Thought you'd always be my
No, when I was 13 I had my first love
There was nobody that compared to my baby and nobody came between us. Don't get ever come above
She had me going crazy. Oh, I was starstruck. She woke me up daily. Don't need no star books
She made my heart pound and skip a beat when I see her in the street and at school on the playground
But I really want to see her on the weekend. She knows she got me days in because she was so amazing
And now my heart is breaking but I just keep on saying
Baby baby
Oh
Thought you'd always be my
My
Baby baby
Oh
Baby
Thought you'd always be my
No, I'm all God
Yeah
I'm all God
Go on
I'm gone